James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Media Files, 1958-2008
  - Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 1981-2006
    - Subseries 2: Audio Cassettes, 1984-2006
      - Tucson Media Monitoring Mary Judge Ryan Radio Ad., September 11, 2000 (Box 224, Folder 84)
      - Tucson Media Monitoring Mary Judge Ryan Radio Ad., September 11, 2000 (Box 224, Folder 85)
      - Tucson Media Monitoring Mary Judge Ryan Radio Ad., September 11, 2000 (Box 224, Folder 86)
      - Tucson Media Monitoring Radio Ad., November 1, 2000 (Box 224, Folder 87)
      - Vic Caputo KTUC (Access copy available), December 17, 1993 (Box 224, Folder 88)
      - Vic Caputo Show (Access copy available), December 6, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 89)
    - Reels, 1987-1990
      This subseries contains reels that cover issues important to Kolbe’s congressional work primarily trade as well as public service announcements. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KAIR, undated (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KATO, undated (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KAVV, undated (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KAYN, undated (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KBBT, undated (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KCKY, undated (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KDAP, undated (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KFBR, undated (Box 225, Folder 8)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KFMM, undated (Box 225, Folder 9)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KGUY, undated (Box 225, Folder 10)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KQEZ, undated (Box 225, Folder 11)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KRUZ, undated (Box 225, Folder 12)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KTAN, undated (Box 225, Folder 13)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KTUC, undated (Box 225, Folder 14)
      - #1 United States Mexico Trade #2 "A New Coin Dollar?" KXMK, undated (Box 225, Folder 15)
      - 5DF Program 10 KAVV, undated (Box 225, Folder 16)
      - 5DF Program 10 KAYN 7:00, Healthcare (Access copy available), June 17, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 17)
      - 5DF Program 10 KCKY, undated (Box 225, Folder 18)
      - 5DF Program 10 KDAP, Catastrophic Healthcare Legislation (Access copy available), August 3, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 19)
      - 5DF Program 10 KGVY, undated (Box 225, Folder 20)
      - 5DF #1 Leg wrap up (Access copy available), 1988 (Box 225, Folder 21)
      - 5DF #2 SSC, Super Collider (Access copy available), 1988 (Box 225, Folder 22)
      - 5DF Program 6 KCKY, "The Maquiladora industry and protectionism" (Access copy available), April 7, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 23)
      - 5DF Program 7 KCKY, "United States Embassy in Soviet Union" (Access copy available), April 28, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 24)
      - 5DF Program 8 KCKY, "Trade legislation recently passed by the House" (Access copy available), June 3, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 25)
      - 5DF Program 10 KFLT, undated (Box 225, Folder 26)
      - Arts PSA :30 Kolbe OQ: Discovery Today!, undated (Box 225, Folder 27)
      - Food Bank PSA's, undated (Box 225, Folder 28)
      - Holiday Sharing Center :30 PSA Congressman Jim Kolbe KIIM-KCUB (Box 225, Folder 29)
      - Kolbe for Congress 1) :30 "Announcement" 2) :60 "Announcement", undated (Box 225, Folder 30)
      - Kolbe for Congress 1) :30 "Announcement" 2) :60 "Announcement", undated (Box 225, Folder 31)
      - Kolbe for Congress 1) :30 "Announcement" 2) :60 "Announcement", undated (Box 225, Folder 32)
      - NRCC Photo Op with President Bush, June 28, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 33)
    - Compact Discs, 2001-2006
      This subseries contains compact discs of some audio material but mostly photographs especially from congressional delegation trips. Some documents such as presentations and other documents are also present.
      - 1000+ List, Former Maxed Contributors Who Have Not Given This Cycle, undated (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - 2005 Government Graphics, undated (Box 226, Folder 2)
      - Afghanistan and Pakistan, November, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 3)
      - Afghanistan 2002, Powerpoint 97, ca. 2002 (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - Anthony Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - Anti-US Sentiment in China & Internet Freedom Project, undated (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - Archive Files Rowdy H: Drive, undated (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - Arizona Illustrated Border Series Parts 1 & 2, July 29, 2003-July 31, 2003 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      - Bisbee-Ed, Medicare, SS, Border, Homeland Security, Sierra Vista-Ed, Medicare, Border, Homeland Security, Green Valley-Medicare, SS, Border, Homeland Security, undated (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - The Bob Edwards Show: Immigration and Border Show #2, March 10, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 10)
      - The Bob Edwards Show: Immigration and Border Show #1, March 9, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 11)
      - Brit Hume-SS Reform, January 26, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 12)
      - Cambodia, August, 2001 (Box 226, Folder 13)
      - Campaign 04 Photos, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 14)
      - Chairman James Kolbe CODEL Kolbe Jordan, Iraq, Syria and Germany, November 7, 2003-November 12, 2003 (Box 226, Folder 15)
      - CODEL Kolbe, May, 2005-June, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 16)
      - CODEL Kolbe, May, 2005-June, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 17)
      - CODEL Kolbe Africa Disc 1, January, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 18)
      - CODEL Kolbe Africa Disc 1, January, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 19)
      - CODEL Kolbe Africa Disc 2, January, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 20)
      - CODEL Kolbe Africa Disc 2, January, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 21)
      - CODEL Kolbe Georgia-Armenia-Azerbaijan, April 7, 2006-April 14, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 22)
      - CODEL Kolbe Georgia-Armenia-Azerbaijan, April 7, 2006-April 14, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 23)
      - CODEL Kolbe Georgia-Armenia-Azerbaijan, April 7, 2006-April 14, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 24)
      - CODEL Kolbe, Kirkuk, Iraq, November, 2003 (Box 226, Folder 25)
      - CODEL Kolbe Lithuania, Ukraine, Austria, October, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 26)
      - CODEL Kolbe Lithuania, Ukraine, Austria, October, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 27)
      - CODEL Kolbe Mali, Ethiopia, Swaziland, Mozambique & South Africa, April 1, 2002-April 10, 2002 (Box 226, Folder 28)
      - CODEL Kolbe Pakistan and Afghanistan, November, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 29)
      - CODEL Kolbe Pakistan and Afghanistan, November, 2005-December, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 30)
      - CODEL Kolbe Uzbekistan-Afghanistan-Jordan-Iraq-Ukraine, December, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 31)
      - Congressional Delegation Antarctica, January, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 32)
      - Congressman John Shadegg Powerpoint Presentation for use at a Social Security Town Hall, undated (Box 226, Folder 33)
      - Congressman Jim Kolbe, Washington, D.C., May, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 34)
      - Congressman Kolbe / Hon. David Walker 28:36, April 27, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 35)
      - Congressman Kolbe with Midshipmen, November 8, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 36)
      - Democracy Beyond the Baltics, Latvia Trip, February 20, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 37)
      - EOS Technologies Ribbon Cutting, February 18, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 38)
      - Eric Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 39)
      - Images of Jan. 13 2005 Reception, Penguin, Other Wildlife, Pressure Ridges, Weather, Mt. Erebus, January 13, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 40)
      - International Conference "The Future of democracy beyond the Baltics", February 6, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 41)
      - Jeremy Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 42)
      - Jim Kolbe Announcement, undated (Box 226, Folder 43)
      - Jim's Outlook Info, undated (Box 226, Folder 44)
      - Juba Assessment, Town Planning and Administration, November, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 45)
      - KC Pictures from Some Trip?, undated (Box 226, Folder 46)
      - Kentucky Campus Centennial Celebration, October 10, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 47)
      - Kolbe #2 Antarctic Pics, January 14, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 48)
      - Kolbe Archives Speeches, Op-Eds, Etc., 2005-2006 (Box 226, Folder 49)
      - Kolbe Steve #1 & 17, undated (Box 226, Folder 50)
      - Kristen Hellmer, Justice O'Connor, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 51)
      - Log Cabin Republicans A Tribute to Rep. Jim Kolbe, April 29, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 52)
      - Mark Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 53)
      - Master Iraq, October 22, 2002 (Box 226, Folder 54)
      - Media Clips: Brit Hume/SS Reform, O'reilly Factor/Secure America Act, July 21, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 55)
      - Messner & Brooks Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 56)
      - New Leaders, New Money: A New Middle East?, May 20, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 57)
      - New Zealand, US-NZ Business Council, 2003 (Box 226, Folder 58)
      - Operation Unified Assistance, January, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 59)
      - O'Reilly Factor Secure America Act, May 24, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 60)
      - Patrick & Aaron Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 61)
      - Petition Signatures, Petition Circulators, Drafts for Volunteer Cards and Thank Yous, undated (Box 226, Folder 62)
      - Photos-Announcement Day, undated (Box 226, Folder 63)
      - Photos by Mavk Westpoint + Naval Visit, undated (Box 226, Folder 64)
      - Phuket/Ranong, undated (Box 226, Folder 65)
      - Public Service Announcement Campaign Hurricane Relief, undated (Box 226, Folder 66)
      - Radio Ad, undated (Box 226, Folder 67)
      - Radio Spots, undated (Box 226, Folder 68)
      - Randy Graf "Upside Down" Ad, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 69)
      - Report to the People 29:34, September, 2001 (Box 226, Folder 70)
      - Rep. Jim Kolbe Washington Journal, March 9, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 71)
      - Rep. Kolbe, October 26, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 72)
      - Rep. Kolbe Statement 3:03, September 15, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 73)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Bernie Ungar & Beth Deisher 28:43, July 19, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 74)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Bernie Ungar & Beth Deisher 28:43, July 19, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 75)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Col. Wood 28:38, February 3, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 76)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Dr. Tim Kane & Bill Carr 28:44, June 22, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 77)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Frank Sharry, Mark Krikorian, Tamar Jacoby & Stephen Dinan #1 29:45, March 2, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 78)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Frank Sharry, Mark Krikorian, Tamar Jacoby & Stephen Dinan #2 28:32, March 2, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 79)
      - Rep. Kolbe w/ Leslie Norwalk 28:46, November 1, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 80)
      - Securing America's Future Through Energy, undated (Box 226, Folder 81)
      - Social Security, Retirement Security.ppt, August 11, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 82)
      - Sudan Codel Photos, undated (Box 226, Folder 83)
      - Summer Townhall Presentation Rough Draft, undated (Box 226, Folder 84)
      - TV Clips, Lou Dobbs/CAFTA, July 27, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 85)
      - TFPHX Brief, CODEL Visit, December 22, 2004 (Box 226, Folder 86)
      - Todd Legislative Info Archive, undated (Box 226, Folder 87)
      - Too Jewish with Rabbi Sam Cohon and Friends, May 4, 2003 (Box 226, Folder 88)
      - Tucson Townhall, undated (Box 226, Folder 89)
      - Tucson Townhall, undated (Box 226, Folder 90)
      - United States-Mexico IPG, Valle de Bravo, Mexico, March 2, 2006-March 5, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 91)
      - United States Ship Abraham Lincoln Congressman Kolbe Visit, January, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 92)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 226, Folder 93)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 226, Folder 94)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 226, Folder 95)
      - Visit of CODEL Kolbe to Lithuania, October 10, 2005-October 12, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 96)
      - Visit of CODEL Kolbe to Lithuania, October 10, 2005-October 12, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 97)
      - W. Sumatra Infrastructure Damage Assessment In Progress As Of 15 Janos, January 15 (Box 226, Folder 98)
      - Your Government: Public Service Announcement Campaign, Honoring our Veterans, November, 2005 (Box 226, Folder 99)
      - Your Government: Public Service Announcement Campaign, Dangers of Drinking and Driving, undated (Box 226, Folder 100)
    - Computer Disks, 1998-2002
      This subseries contains computer disks with materials related to Kolbe’s campaigns, fundraising, staff files and press.
      - 1000, September 25, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - 2001 PC's, Cochise County PC's, Cochise County E-Mails (Box 227, Folder 2)
      - $25+ Tucson/Cochise Donors, April 3, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 3)
      - 500, September 25, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 4)
      - 500+, September 16, 2002 (Box 227, Folder 5)
      - 750, undated (Box 227, Folder 6)
      - 98 Phx PV Scotts 250+, 1998 (Box 227, Folder 7)
      - Announcement, 2002 (Box 227, Folder 8)
      - Arizona Press List!, undated (Box 227, Folder 9)
      - AZ Star Questionnaire Tech Address List, undated (Box 227, Folder 10)
      - Back Up Disc, undated (Box 227, Folder 11)
      - Birthday, 2002 (Box 227, Folder 12)
      - Click Finance Team, Kolbe Finance Team, Click-Kolbe Finance Team, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 13)
      - Cochise 25 + Cochise (All), July 25, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 14)
      - Council/Dome, undated (Box 227, Folder 15)
      - Disk 8, undated (Box 227, Folder 16)
      - Dome Club, Kolbe Council, undated (Box 227, Folder 17)
      - Dome Club-Oct Trip 2001, Houselist, August 5, 2001-October, 2001 (Box 227, Folder 18)
      - Donors, September 27, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 19)
      - Donors, GV, Sahuarita/Nogales/Rio Rico, June 1, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 20)
      - Doug Nick's Press Files, undated (Box 227, Folder 21)
      - Doug Nick's Press Files, undated (Box 227, Folder 22)
      - Doug Nick's Press Files, undated (Box 227, Folder 23)
      - Doug Nick's Press Files, undated (Box 227, Folder 24)
      - E-mail Update List, undated (Box 227, Folder 25)
      - Espinzoza Fundraiser, undated (Box 227, Folder 26)
      - Export, Maricopa, 131 Names, undated (Box 227, Folder 27)
      - File: Script for Callers, undated (Box 227, Folder 28)
      - Focus on Energy and the Economy, undated (Box 227, Folder 29)
      - Ford Press, Former HC, May Propsects, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 30)
      - GRN 2000 SOVC, undated (Box 227, Folder 31)
      - GV/Sahuarita/Rio Rico, June 27, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 32)
      - HASERT Checkin, RSVP, Seats, Contributions, FC, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 33)
      - Hastert Event, January 20, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 34)
      - Healthcare, Education, 1998 (Box 227, Folder 35)
      - Kolbe 2000, December 5, 1999 (Box 227, Folder 36)
      - Kolbe 2000 50+, May 19, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 37)
      - Kolbe Donors, August 14, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 38)
      - Kolbe Rolley, undated (Box 227, Folder 39)
      - Kolbe Stuff, 1998 (Box 227, Folder 40)
      - Kolbe Team 2000 Stuff, HC Lists, Media Info, undated (Box 227, Folder 41)
      - List-Donors, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 42)
      - Media Advisory, undated (Box 227, Folder 43)
      - PC List, May 3, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 44)
      - PC List, December, 1999 (Box 227, Folder 45)
      - Petition Walkers-List C Letter, May 2, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 46)
      - Priebe Resume, undated (Box 227, Folder 47)
      - PV-Phx Scotts Donors 250+, 2000 (Box 227, Folder 48)
      - Stuff, 1000+, 2000-2002 (Box 227, Folder 49)
      - Untitled, August 5, 2001 (Box 227, Folder 50)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 227, Folder 51)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 227, Folder 52)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 227, Folder 53)
      - Walkup Letter-B-day, Downloads: Grassroots, undated (Box 227, Folder 54)
  - Series 3: Memorabilia, 1984-2005
    This series contains plaques, awards and certificates from Kolbe’s congressional career. Also included are guest books, buttons, campaign posters and pens used for signing legislation.
    - Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Buttons (1 of 3), 1986-1990 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Buttons (2 of 3), 1986-1990 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Buttons (3 of 3), 1986-1990 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Certificate: Award for the Completion of Phase I of the Kabul to Kandahar Highway, February 20, 2004 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Certificate: F-16 Fighting Falcon Acknowledgement, June 20, 1986 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Certificate: Various, 1984-2004 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Dominoes: XXVI Reunion Interparlamentaria Mexico-Estados Unidos De America Dominoes, June, 1987 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Ephemera, 2004 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Guest Book: Visitor's Register, January 1, 1984-January 12, 1999 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Guest Book, 1985-1986 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Guest Book, 1987-1988 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Guest Book, 1988-1989 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Guest Book, 1989-1992 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Guest Book, 1999-2006 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Guest Book, 2001-2005 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Guest Book, 2006 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Identification Card: United States House of Representatives, January, 2003-January, 2005 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - License Plates: Congressional, 1991-2004 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - License Plates: Presidential Inauguration/Bicentennial (2), 1989 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Pen: Presidential Pen, George H.W. Bush, undated (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Pen: Presidential Pen, Bill Clinton, December 10, 1993 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Plaque: Air Force Association Tucson Chapter Presidents Award, May 29, 1990 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Plaque: Congressional Fire Services Caucus Member in Good Standing, April 30, 1991 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Plaque: Congressional Hispanic Caucus Honorary Member, 1987 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Plaque: Enactment of Public Law 102-231 Award, March 4, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Plaque: House of Representatives (1 of 2), undated (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Plaque: House of Representatives (2 of 2), undated (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Plaque: Independent Unsurance Agents of Arizona Legislative Achievement Award, June 10, 1980 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Plaque: Key to City of Taichung, undated (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Plaque: Santa Cruz 2nd Annual Massing of the Colors Patriotic Achievement Award, May 16, 1987 (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Plaque: United States Ship Tucson SSN-770, undated (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Plaque: Wilderness Dedication: Arizona Desert Wilderness Act of 1990, April 6, 1991 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Series 4: Oversize, 1988-2006
    This series contains oversized materials from other series including correspondence, photographs and memorabilia.
    - Constituent Mail: United States Ship Nimitz CVN-68 Thank-You Letter, undated (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Congressman Jim Kolbe and Women's Legal Rights Initiative Benin Coordinator Elvire Ahounou Houenassou view public awareness booklets on the Benin Family Code, Cotonou, Benin, January 5, 2006 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Don Hodel with Kolbe and others at signing, undated (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: James Webb with Kolbe, McCain and others, undated (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Kolbe in group shot, Jordan Gateway Projects, Congressional Delegation visit, April 22, 2001 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with Dennis Hastert, undated (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with Dick Cheney, undated (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with James Baker, undated (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with J.C. Watts, Jr., undated (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with Robert H. Michel, undated (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with unidentified, October, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Kolbe with unidentified, undated (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Memorabilia: Campaign Poster (2), undated (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Memorabilia: Copy of Arizona-Idaho Conservation Act, November 18, 1988 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - Memorabilia: Copy of the Cave Creek Canyon Protection Act of 1993 with Presidential Pen, August 2, 1993 (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - Jim Kolbe copper bar donated by Phelps Dodge, undated (Box 232)